<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on realjame</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on realjame</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Website snowstorm effect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-12-27-snowstorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-12-27-snowstorm/</guid>
      <description>For the holidays, I added a simple snowing effect.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s not actually my code, but I did make a simple control to toggle the snow effect.&#xA;Adding the snowing effect I was playing around with the classic snowstorm.js script by Scott Schiller, but I could never get it to properly turn on and off without requiring a page reload when making button. Plus, it always looked super distracting no matter what I did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wanna cut down on phone usage? Try a smartwatch!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-25-smartwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-25-smartwatch/</guid>
      <description>Buy an expensive companion for your phone, and that&amp;rsquo;ll lead you to use your phone less? It sounds like an oxymoron. But after over a month of using my Google Pixel Watch, it seems to be true!&#xA;So, yeah. I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with spending more time on my phone than I&amp;rsquo;d like. And I try stuff like time tracking apps, blocking, etc. but nothing works. Quite simply, if my phone was there, I would be on it, such as before going to bed and then immediately waking up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will people glorify the current internet in 20 years?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-21-glorification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-21-glorification/</guid>
      <description>For the last few years, there&amp;rsquo;s been low-stakes movements to rediscover the aesthetics and values that composed of the Web 1.0 era internet - that is, from the 90s to the early/mid 2000s.&#xA;{% include image.html url=&amp;quot;/note/media/glorification-neocities.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;ldquo;Index page for websites people have made on Neocities&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Neocities is a modern-day platform for website creation and hosting, which people commonly use for their personal, sometimes Web 1.0 themed, websites.&amp;rdquo; %}&#xA;I find it fun, why do you think this site is here in the first place?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-08-hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-08-hi/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write another daily note. (I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to.)&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m not dead. That&amp;rsquo;s the most important thing! Now you know.&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to show for any projects at the moment. That doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I haven&amp;rsquo;t done anything or I&amp;rsquo;ve abandoned them; just that they aren&amp;rsquo;t complete enough to present.&#xA;That&amp;rsquo;s the reason there haven&amp;rsquo;t been any blog/devlog posts. For the near future, I only want to share completed work and not just discuss what I&amp;rsquo;m dreaming of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spooking Out 1 year anniversary!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-1-spooking-out-1-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-1-spooking-out-1-year/</guid>
      <description>November is upon us! Did you have a good Halloween? And are you aware that Spooking Out, the 2010 Roblox game by me and a friend, is now a year old (give or take a few days)?&#xA;We have no idea if it&amp;rsquo;s been hosted and played by other people independently in this time. But a few weeks ago, my friend hosted a server for it, and people still like the game!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Octoprint is very cool!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-22-octoprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-22-octoprint/</guid>
      <description>Setting up a remote control / web UI for my 3D printer was a game changer, I regret doing this sooner. Give OctoPrint a try!&#xA;Do you think 3D printing is cool? My dad bought a 3D printer for the both of us last year, but it went mostly unused due to some issues with calibration and also just, kinda getting lazy.&#xA;But I set everything up again, and somehow, after doing nothing but collect dust for 4 months, it prints better than when I was actively calibrating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚛️ React: When everything looks like a nail...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-12-web-frameworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-12-web-frameworks/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on textarea.site as a way to dive back into the beautiful and the ugly parts of front-end web development. After a few days of work, I decided to rewrite the entire project in Svelte. Surprising? Maybe not. It&amp;rsquo;s about the right tool for the job, and here, React is not it.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m sure people have written countless times about this. But it&amp;rsquo;s true that being versatile is one of the best skills you can have as a software developer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailbreaking a Kindle Voyage and installing KOReader</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-08-18-kindle-jailbreak/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-08-18-kindle-jailbreak/</guid>
      <description>I love my 2014 Kindle Voyage, actively been using it for almost 10 years now. But after finding out update support ended a while ago, why not finally jailbreak it and install more open and featureful e-reader software?&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m new to KOReader, so I&amp;rsquo;ll have to see if I actually like using it as a daily driver. But it can&amp;rsquo;t hurt to try, and at the very least, liberating the device might come in handy in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing the latest Ruby with rbenv on Debian</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-08-16-ruby-debian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-08-16-ruby-debian/</guid>
      <description>I decided to switch from running Ruby natively on Windows to WSL, because Ruby on Windows is pretty bad. Installing the rbenv tool to manage multiple versions of Ruby is simple, but in order to add (by compiling) a Ruby version, there are a few dependencies to install.&#xA;For context, rbenv is a version manager tool for Ruby. This allows me to have multiple versions of Ruby installed at once and switch between at any time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spooking Out&#39;s Modern Roblox Port</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022-11-02-spooking-out-modern-roblox-port/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022-11-02-spooking-out-modern-roblox-port/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone, I am proud to announce the modern Roblox port of Spooking Out! has been published to the Roblox website!&#xA;Don&amp;rsquo;t know about Spooking Out? Read the [previous article]({% post_url /blog/2022-10-24-introducing-spooking-out %}).&#xA;This means you can now play our game on modern Roblox. Oh, and we also went back and improved the experience to make playing it on mobile, controller, and Xbox just as playable and fun!&#xA;Play it here!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Spooking Out!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022-10-24-introducing-spooking-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022-10-24-introducing-spooking-out/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m proud to announce a brand new game made for the classic Roblox engine (2010 specifically), made in collaboration with my friend, Tobu.fi.&#xA;Come play the game with us on a 24/7 server I&amp;rsquo;m hosting for the game, or download a copy of the game for yourself.&#xA;Client: 2010L IP: court-michelle.at.playit.gg Port: 41927 Map: Spooking Out! Players: 12 Version: Novetus 1.3 v8.2022.1 Not sure how long I will keep this server running&amp;hellip; at least until Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Opera 8 quirks with the simple layout</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-03-14-opera8-quirks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-03-14-opera8-quirks/</guid>
      <description>I was testing this with Opera 8. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure which version the DSi browser was built on (my target when making this layout), so I just went for the lowest one, and a bit lower to be safe: Opera 8.&#xA;So, here are 2 quick little quirks I noticed that occured in Opera 8, but not in my modern browser.&#xA;I could put clean this up but I&amp;rsquo;m lazy and I&amp;rsquo;ll just share the quick notes I took.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotics competition and solar eclipse and stuff</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023-10-15-space-coast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023-10-15-space-coast/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday, September 14, I went to the Space Coast Showdown, an off-season robotics competition with my team.&#xA;I say &amp;ldquo;my&amp;rdquo; team, but I am new to the club. It was worth it to take the whole day off to be there and support everyone. I also learned a lot for how I can help contribute in the feature, as well as what competitions are truly like!&#xA;{% include image.html url=&amp;quot;/blog/media/spacecoast-place_small.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple layout, why not?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2024-03-13-simple-layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2024-03-13-simple-layout/</guid>
      <description>I made an alternate, minimal version of my website. You can find it on the sidebar, or head to simple.realja.me.&#xA;{% include image.html url=&amp;quot;/blog/media/simple-home_small.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;ldquo;Screenshot of the simple layout&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Rendered in Opera 8, a browser from 2005&amp;rdquo; %}&#xA;Now, you can read my website on practically any web browser and device ever made!&#xA;{% include image.html url=&amp;quot;/blog/media/simple-nav_small.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;ldquo;The navigation menu displayed on a red Nintendo DSi&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Running on a Nintendo DSi!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking about the simple layout</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-03-14-simple-layout-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-03-14-simple-layout-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I think it&amp;rsquo;s kinda funny that I am motivated to make this alternate version, but not to actually write posts.&#xA;That&amp;rsquo;s what I was thinking while making it: ok, I can access this site from anywhere. But what is there to read?&#xA;I feel like this is a common occurence with a lot of blogs out there, especially ones by web developers: most likely only a few posts, and the majority of them are simply explaining how the site was implemented, in whatever static site generator or CSS styling they picked.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
