<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roblox on realjame</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/roblox/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Roblox on realjame</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/roblox/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>hi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-08-hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-08-hi/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write another daily note. (I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to.)&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m not dead. That&amp;rsquo;s the most important thing! Now you know.&#xA;I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to show for any projects at the moment. That doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I haven&amp;rsquo;t done anything or I&amp;rsquo;ve abandoned them; just that they aren&amp;rsquo;t complete enough to present.&#xA;That&amp;rsquo;s the reason there haven&amp;rsquo;t been any blog/devlog posts. For the near future, I only want to share completed work and not just discuss what I&amp;rsquo;m dreaming of.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spooking Out 1 year anniversary!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-1-spooking-out-1-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-1-spooking-out-1-year/</guid>
      <description>November is upon us! Did you have a good Halloween? And are you aware that Spooking Out, the 2010 Roblox game by me and a friend, is now a year old (give or take a few days)?&#xA;We have no idea if it&amp;rsquo;s been hosted and played by other people independently in this time. But a few weeks ago, my friend hosted a server for it, and people still like the game!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September Status</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-03-september-status/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-03-september-status/</guid>
      <description>Day 3 of September. Things are going OK for me, I just wanted to write down here what I&amp;rsquo;m aiming for this month. Right now, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on college applications and web development projects, so Roblox stuff will keep taking a back seat.&#xA;I wrote on my Projects page that the new Project Micrathena will resume development this month. I hope I will find time to work on it, but it will likely be at the end of September, and not the start as hoped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spooking Out&#39;s Modern Roblox Port</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022-11-02-spooking-out-modern-roblox-port/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022-11-02-spooking-out-modern-roblox-port/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone, I am proud to announce the modern Roblox port of Spooking Out! has been published to the Roblox website!&#xA;Don&amp;rsquo;t know about Spooking Out? Read the [previous article]({% post_url /blog/2022-10-24-introducing-spooking-out %}).&#xA;This means you can now play our game on modern Roblox. Oh, and we also went back and improved the experience to make playing it on mobile, controller, and Xbox just as playable and fun!&#xA;Play it here!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Spooking Out!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022-10-24-introducing-spooking-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2022-10-24-introducing-spooking-out/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m proud to announce a brand new game made for the classic Roblox engine (2010 specifically), made in collaboration with my friend, Tobu.fi.&#xA;Come play the game with us on a 24/7 server I&amp;rsquo;m hosting for the game, or download a copy of the game for yourself.&#xA;Client: 2010L IP: court-michelle.at.playit.gg Port: 41927 Map: Spooking Out! Players: 12 Version: Novetus 1.3 v8.2022.1 Not sure how long I will keep this server running&amp;hellip; at least until Halloween.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
