<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bookmark on realjame</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/bookmark/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bookmark on realjame</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/bookmark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🔗🎞️ Cheesy Hfj: &#39;i am frustrated&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-02-26-cheesyhfj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-02-26-cheesyhfj/</guid>
      <description>I am frustrated about being frustrated about this many things.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m frustrated about how many days I&amp;rsquo;ve spent feeling frustrated. I could have spent that time talking with my good friend, or taking a walk through neighborhood, or creating pieces of stunning, incredible art.&#xA;While thinking of all the reasons that make me frustrated, I started to get frustrated&amp;hellip; funny how that stuff works out.&#xA;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jadp64OvrZk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔗 Livakivi, a cool and motivating YouTube channel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-12-28-livakivi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-12-28-livakivi/</guid>
      <description>Hey, check out Livakivi on YouTube.&#xA;He makes videos about a few topics, such as learning Japanese, learning art, working out, etc. But at their core, he makes videos about self-improvement and working to be better, to expand your mind and body every day.&#xA;I was very, very inactive not only on the blog, but on all projects and skills I&amp;rsquo;m learning in November and part of December. What helped me get back into the swing of things and with better disclipine was his videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🔗 James Somers: &#39;More people should write&#39; (2012)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-20-jsomers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-20-jsomers/</guid>
      <description>That’s the promise: you will live more curiously if you write. You will become a scientist, if not of the natural world than of whatever world you care about. More of that world will pop alive. You will see more when you look at it.&#xA;Read it: https://jsomers.net/blog/more-people-should-write&#xA;Fantastic, inspiring post. I&amp;rsquo;ve kept journals the whole year because of this, and I won&amp;rsquo;t stop.&#xA;Writing, being able to format and output thoughts in your mind, is one of the most effective tools for better valuing and reflecting on each day that goes by.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
