<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web on realjame</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web on realjame</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Website snowstorm effect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-12-27-snowstorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-12-27-snowstorm/</guid>
      <description>For the holidays, I added a simple snowing effect.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s not actually my code, but I did make a simple control to toggle the snow effect.&#xA;Adding the snowing effect I was playing around with the classic snowstorm.js script by Scott Schiller, but I could never get it to properly turn on and off without requiring a page reload when making button. Plus, it always looked super distracting no matter what I did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will people glorify the current internet in 20 years?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-21-glorification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-11-21-glorification/</guid>
      <description>For the last few years, there&amp;rsquo;s been low-stakes movements to rediscover the aesthetics and values that composed of the Web 1.0 era internet - that is, from the 90s to the early/mid 2000s.&#xA;{% include image.html url=&amp;quot;/note/media/glorification-neocities.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;ldquo;Index page for websites people have made on Neocities&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Neocities is a modern-day platform for website creation and hosting, which people commonly use for their personal, sometimes Web 1.0 themed, websites.&amp;rdquo; %}&#xA;I find it fun, why do you think this site is here in the first place?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on corru.observer (it&#39;s very cool)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-25-corru-observer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-25-corru-observer/</guid>
      <description>corru.observer is a very strange website. It&amp;rsquo;s an interactive story that&amp;rsquo;s part 3D game, part visual novel, part website. Hypertext fiction at its finest.&#xA;When I stumbled across it, I basically spent the rest of my night playing it for 3 hours straight. It&amp;rsquo;s right up my wheelhouse, and great stuff!! I really do not want to say anything about what corru.observer is about. If you think you are interested, stop reading and play it now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⚛️ React: When everything looks like a nail...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-12-web-frameworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2023-09-12-web-frameworks/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on textarea.site as a way to dive back into the beautiful and the ugly parts of front-end web development. After a few days of work, I decided to rewrite the entire project in Svelte. Surprising? Maybe not. It&amp;rsquo;s about the right tool for the job, and here, React is not it.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m sure people have written countless times about this. But it&amp;rsquo;s true that being versatile is one of the best skills you can have as a software developer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update III - A Complete Redesign</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023-08-30-update-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2023-08-30-update-3/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this time I don&amp;rsquo;t want to write about myself too much. Just the website. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent almost 2 weeks now working on this big redesign, I really hope you like it!&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s a sidebar instead of the old header. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a more effective use of desktop screen space, and on mobile, it turns into a horizontally scrolling top bar! I was inspired by Zenith&amp;rsquo;s website in terms of design.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Opera 8 quirks with the simple layout</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-03-14-opera8-quirks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-03-14-opera8-quirks/</guid>
      <description>I was testing this with Opera 8. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure which version the DSi browser was built on (my target when making this layout), so I just went for the lowest one, and a bit lower to be safe: Opera 8.&#xA;So, here are 2 quick little quirks I noticed that occured in Opera 8, but not in my modern browser.&#xA;I could put clean this up but I&amp;rsquo;m lazy and I&amp;rsquo;ll just share the quick notes I took.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple layout, why not?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2024-03-13-simple-layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2024-03-13-simple-layout/</guid>
      <description>I made an alternate, minimal version of my website. You can find it on the sidebar, or head to simple.realja.me.&#xA;{% include image.html url=&amp;quot;/blog/media/simple-home_small.png&amp;quot; alt=&amp;ldquo;Screenshot of the simple layout&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Rendered in Opera 8, a browser from 2005&amp;rdquo; %}&#xA;Now, you can read my website on practically any web browser and device ever made!&#xA;{% include image.html url=&amp;quot;/blog/media/simple-nav_small.jpg&amp;quot; alt=&amp;ldquo;The navigation menu displayed on a red Nintendo DSi&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Running on a Nintendo DSi!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking about the simple layout</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-03-14-simple-layout-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/notes/2024-03-14-simple-layout-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I think it&amp;rsquo;s kinda funny that I am motivated to make this alternate version, but not to actually write posts.&#xA;That&amp;rsquo;s what I was thinking while making it: ok, I can access this site from anywhere. But what is there to read?&#xA;I feel like this is a common occurence with a lot of blogs out there, especially ones by web developers: most likely only a few posts, and the majority of them are simply explaining how the site was implemented, in whatever static site generator or CSS styling they picked.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
